Every murder lives on.
Oddity is a horror, mystery film directed by Damian McCarthy.
After the brutal murder of her twin sister, Darcy goes after those
responsible by using haunted items as her tools for revenge.
Dani Timmis / Darcy Odello, played by Carolyn Bracken.
Ted Timmis, played by Gwilym Lee.
Ivan, played by Steve Wall.
Bernie, played by Joe Rooney.
Olin Boole, played by Tadhg Murphy.
Yana, played by Caroline Menton.
Oddity is a 2024 Irish horror film written and directed by Damian McCarthy.
It follows a blind medium and curio shopkeeper who is still grieving the death of her twin sister a year prior when a
wooden golem from her collection becomes crucial to her quest to uncover the truth about her sister's murder.
The film premiered at South by Southwest on 8 March 2024, where it won the
Audience Award in the Midnighter section of the festival.
It was released in Ireland and the United Kingdom on 30 August 2024.
The film explores themes of mannequin, paranormal, murder, home invasion, twins.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.